Okay, first one is ICICI Lombard, here I am
giving the buy level of 1633 futures, 1633 is your stop loss
level for the target of 1680 and 1695,
okay, the results came yesterday, very good, the
results are much better than expected
on every parameter, I did not expect such
good numbers, second thing is that there is a
report from Jefferies with a target of 1950, it is already maintained,
CLS may have downgraded but
with that it has increased the target, it has
not reduced the target, HSBC has a target of 1990,
I think if
you look at the numbers from the point of view of net premium one also, it has
come better than expected, the profit has come better, the
numbers are good on every parameter, you should like this stock